[{"question": "What is the input file in a C program building process.?", "option1": "A) filename.k", "option2": "B) filename.cpp", "option3": "C) filename.c", "option4": "D) filename.p", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output Filename of C Program build process.?", "option1": "A) filename.ex", "option2": "B) filename.bak", "option3": "C) filename.exe", "option4": "D) filename.asm", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the first step in C program building process.?", "option1": "A) Compiling", "option2": "B) Assembling", "option3": "C) Linking", "option4": "D) Preprocessing", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the next step to Preprocessing in C Program build process.?", "option1": "A) Compiling", "option2": "B) Assembling", "option3": "C) Linking", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "What is the next step to Compiling in C program build process.?", "option1": "A) Preprocessing", "option2": "B) Assembling", "option3": "C) Linking", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the next step to Assembling in C program build process.?", "option1": "A) Preprocessing", "option2": "B) Compiling", "option3": "C) Linking", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is a C Editor.?", "option1": "A) A C compiler", "option2": "B) A C assembler", "option3": "C) A C code editor like notepad", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Compiler compiling.?", "option1": "A) An assembly language code", "option2": "B) Object Code", "option3": "C) Class file code", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "Expanded Source code is the output of which C program building process.?", "option1": "A) Preprocessor", "option2": "B) Assembler", "option3": "C) Linker", "option4": "D) Compiler", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " Choose a correct statement about C program output file.?", "option1": "A) Output file .exe is machine dependent. .Exe is windows suitable file.", "option2": "B) Exe file does not work in Linux or Unix machines. So different type of output is created on different machines", "option3": "C) Linker produces a suitable output file for each maching", "option4": "D) All the above", "ans": "D"}]
